tradingstrategyguides.com 2019-07-23

# Privacy Policy | Trading Strategy Guides

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Trading Strategy Guides ([www.tradingstrategyguides.com](https://tradingstrategyguides.com/)). On some pages, you can make requests, register as a member, or order additional products & services. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Email address
  * Timezone
  * Trading style – for example: your preferred risk
  * Information about your trading accounts, which can be real or fictional
  * Your mobile/cell phone number (for SMS alerts)

We do not collect credit/debit card data or your billing address details. This information is recorded by the payment processing company (paypal.com, recurly.com, or authorize.net).

Under no circumstances do we collect any personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life.

When you visit our Website, our computers may automatically collect statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally but rather identifies information about a visit to our Website. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our Website, the user’s IP address, which pages people visit, from which domains our visitors come and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit for aggregation purposes only. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our Website.

We only use “cookies” as described in this Section. A “cookie” is a piece of information that our Web site sends to your browser, which then stores this information on your system. If a cookie is used, our Website will be able to “remember” information about you and your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie. Many users prefer to use cookies in order to help them navigate a Web site as seamlessly as possible. You should be aware that cookies contain no more information than you volunteer, and they are not able to “invade” your hard drive and return to the sender personal or other information from your computer.

Our uses of “cookies” are limited to the following specific situation. That situation is with respect to temporary cookies. There are two instances in which we use temporary cookies. First, if you are accessing our services through one of our online applications our Web server may automatically send your browser a temporary cookie, which is used to help your browser navigate our Website. The only information contained in these temporary cookies is a direction value that lets our software determine which page to show when you hit the back button in your browser. This bit of information is erased when you close your current browser window. If you come to our Website from one of our business partners, our Web server may also send your browser a temporary cookie that reflects an “origination code” for that business partner. We use this information for statistical and marketing purposes.

We use your name and email address so that we can email you in regard to information that you have requested. We use the additional registration information to set up your membership profile.

We may use your mobile /cell phone number to send automated SMS alerts for trading signals or news event warnings. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the payment or registration process.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers.

For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We work to protect your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you provide online at our Web Site. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information, continue to assess new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, upgrade our information security systems.

Protecting the privacy of the young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.  
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can unsubscribe from our email list(s) at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe button at the bottom of one of the emails sent to you. Alternatively, you can request removal from our lists by sending an email to info@tradingstrategyguides.com.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at info@tradingstrategyguides.com.

Trading foreign exchange on margin carries a high level of risk, and may not be suitable for all investors. The high degree of leverage can work against you as well as for you. Before deciding to invest in foreign exchange you should carefully consider your investment objectives, level of experience, and risk appetite. No information or opinion contained on this site should be taken as a solicitation or offer to buy or sell any currency, equity or other financial instruments or services. Past performance is no indication or guarantee of future performance.

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Statement, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on our Website and without any other notice to you.  Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on our Website.
